Moving doesn’t fail because people don’t plan.
It fails because they get bad information early.
Here’s what to lock in first:
One: timing.
Book your removals team as soon as your date is likely.
Don’t wait until everything is final.
Good slots go quickly.
Two: volume.
Most quote mistakes happen when item lists are incomplete.
Share room-by-room details,
including stairs, access, and large furniture.
Three: total cost.
Don’t just compare headline price.
Ask what’s included:
packing, disassembly, waiting time, mileage, insurance.
That’s how Marley Moves works:
clear quotes, practical planning, dependable team.
Send your postcode and ideal date,
and we’ll send a no-obligation quote.